Guide to the David S. Brown papers, 1915-1989 MS0001.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1953-1987; MS0001 Series 2; 3.5 Linear feet (Box 12, Box 10, Box 11, Box 8, Box 9, Box 6, Box 7)
  - The Public Advisory Board and the Tariff Study ICP Case Series: #30, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Administration, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Advice on Advisory Committees, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - A Guide to The Use of Advisory Committees, 07/1959 --08/1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Members Have Responsibilities, Too, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Some Questions in Retrospect, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Report on Alcohol and Tobacco Tax Permissive Training Committee, 08/1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Individual Freedom in Traditional Management: Some Situational Examples, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The Lecture, 12/1960 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - The Federal Government and the Cities, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - How You Can Use the Problem Meeting, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Bureaucracy: Pakistani and American, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - The First Seminar on Public Administration, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - The Staff Man Looks in the Mirror, 06/1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - The Ultimate Managerial Challenge: Creative Change, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - The Brownlow Committee, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - To Read and Reread, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Importance of Understanding Objectives, 03/1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Heart of Policy Development, 04/1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Personnel Officer's New Dilemma, 07/1964 --08/1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - The Key to Self-Help: Improving the Administrative Capabilities of the Aid-Receiving Countries, 06/1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Man Trap: The Deputy Chief, 10/1964 --12/1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Subordinates' Views of Ineffective Executive Behavior, 12/1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - When Nothing Succeeds Like Excess, 07/1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Assistant Chief: Asset or Liability, 05/1965 --06/1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - The Important New Role of Training, 04/1965 --06/1965 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - An Old Tool Holds New Promise for Management, 11/1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Capitalizing on Committees, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Posdcorb Revisited and Revised, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Leader Looks at Authority and Responsibility, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Committees for Community Shelter Planning, 06/1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Speaker Will Answer Questions..., 06/1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Shaping the Organization to Fit People, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Testing Your Management I.Q., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The President and the Bureaus: Time for a Renewal of Relationships, 09/1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Some Feedback on Feedback, 01/1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Why Delegation Works - And Why It Doesn't, 01/1967 --02/1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Businessman and Government Administration, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - The High Cost of Hierarchy, 01/1967 --03/1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The Citizen Committee, Advice or Consent, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The Individual and the Organization: Some Factors Bearing Upon Their Relationship, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Making Decisions, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The PennyWorth Papers: Government Perpetration of Economics, Efficiency, Foresight, Management, and Revealed, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Leader Looks at the Use of Time, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Management of Advisory Committees: An Assignment for the '70's, 07/1972 --08/1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New Approach to Problem Solving, 11/1973 --12/1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Management by Objectives: Promise and Problems, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Need an Assistant Manager?, 07/1975 --08/1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Barriers to Success, 12/1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Role of Training in the Changeover of Governmental Administration, 01/1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Latest Shortage: Skilled Managers, 03/1977 --04/1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - The Constructive Uses of Conflict, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rethinking the Supervisory Role, 11/1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Looking Ahead: The Manager's Job in the Year 2000, 11/1977 --12/1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - TV Keeps Vulgarizing America, 10/07/1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Rethinking the Supervisory Role, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Looking Ahead: The Manager's Job in the Year 2000, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Leadership and Followership: The Twin Ingredients, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Large Organizations and their Deficiencies, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The Myth of Reorganizing, 06/1979 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - An Amicus Curea Speaks Up, 09/15/1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Military Contributions to Management, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Power Problems at the Managerial Level, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - The Chain of Command: What Is Happening To It?, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - How Breakable is the Chain of Command, 01/1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Survey Finds Federal Bureaucracy too Slow, 01/15/1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Middle Managers and Important Company Resources, 02/01/1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Zmiany Utunkcuonowanij Administracji Amerykannskeiej, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Latest Shortage: Skilled and Capable Managers, 05/1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Why Subordinates don't do What They are Asked to Do - And Why They Do, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Fifth Freedom: Freedom from Supervision, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - If You Ask Me: Being Boss is ..., 03/08/1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Japanese Productivity-Lessons for Us?, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Productivity: Why we Must Improve, 08/1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Productivity: Why we Must Improve Part II, 10/1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Managerial Ethic and Productivity Improvement, 09/1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Manager's Responsibilities for Productivity Improvement, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Productivity of the Professionals, 10/1983 --12/1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Future Directions in Financial Management- An Educator's View, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Management Development in the Public Sector, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - New Principles of Management, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - If Necessity is the Mother of Invention, Who is the Father?, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - The Manager's Responsibility for Improvement, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Presidential Power and Managing the Bureaucracy, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - How to Cause Stress in Others, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - A Vezetoi Etika Es A Tiermelekenyseg, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Ink Claims Heritage Advice Doesn't Follow Reagan's Line, 04/22/1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Ten Rules for All Political Appointees, 01/21/1985 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Feds and the Bureaucratic Image Problem, 02/11/1985 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Efficiency Not Meant to be a Government's Cornerstone, 04/22/1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Shapes of Red Cloud Crystal Block Visions, 03/25/1985 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Actually, There Were Some Positive Aspects to Grace Stodl, 04/15/1985 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - The Case for a New Managerial Ethic, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Modeling the Federal Government, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - How the Competition Does It, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Getting Menial Jobs Done, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - A Vezetoi Etika Es A Termelekenyseg II.Resz, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - A Professor Looks at his Profession, 10/15/1986 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Managing the Large Organization: Issues, Ideas, recepts, Innovations, 11/1986 --12/1986 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - A Brown Sampler: Management and Other Matters, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - The New Managers and their Responsibilities, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Figuring Everyone into Budget Planning, 03/1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - The Telephone- And How to Manage it, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Management by Tergiversation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Management: How and Where It Originated, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Selection and Development of Senior Administrators, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - How to Make Quality Decisions, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Additional writings, ca. 1960-1989; MS0001 Series 3; 2 Linear feet (Box 15, Box 16, Box 13, Box 14)
  This series contains newspaper articles, travelogues, and other personal writings by David S. Brown from approximately the 1960s through the 1980s.
  - Laws: Writings dealing with personal creeds, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Quotes: Various sayings from DSB, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Rejected Material: Articles not accepted for publication, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Anecdotes, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - College: Various Papers and Planned Debate Speeches written while at school, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - College: Poetry and Drawings from early in DSB's life, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - College: Poetry and Drawings from early in DSB's life, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Management: Several written pages about miscellaneous management topics, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Articles: An Assortment of writings published in the Washington Post and smaller papers, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Down East: A publication from Maine, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Elections: Articles on how to predict elections, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - You Can't Get There From Here, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 1, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 3, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 4, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 5, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 6, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 7, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 8, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 9, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 10, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 11, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 12, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 13, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 14, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 15, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 16, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 17, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 18, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - You Can't Get There From Here: Chapter 20, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Travelogues: Conquest of Katahdin, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Travelouges: On the trail of the Lobster Primeval, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Travelouges: The Middle Aged Man and the Sea, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Travelouges: Americana the Beautiful, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Travelouges: The Flowered State, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Travelouges: The Day the Sun Set Twice, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Travelouges: The Last of the Lower Forty-Eight, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Travelouges: Moby Dog, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Travelouges: Why Don't They Ever Tell You it's a Holiday, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Travelouges: Dr. Brown, I Presume, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Travelouges: El Salvador, Superstar, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Travelouges: Bermuda Short, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Travelouges: Flow Gently, Sweet Amazon, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Travelouges: Tea-Bag Time Along the Thames, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Travelouges: It's Getting Longer Every Year 1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Travelouges: The French Connection -- Reaffirmed, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Travelouges: The Big Blizzards of 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Travelouges: All Things Big and Bountiful, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Travelouges: Born Again -- In Poland this Time, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Travelouges: Some New Light on the Dark Continent, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Travelouges: The Long, Hot, Sultry Summer of 1982 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Travelouges: Europe, in Heat, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - History of the Lovett Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Letters explaining the death of ELB, 05/27/1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pakistan, 1960 ca. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    A series of articles published while in Pakistan in the early 1960s.
  - Anfractuosities, 01/15/1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Order of the Purple Clam certificates, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - DSB's Multiple Choice Test, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Travelogue: The Browns Abroad, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pass Yourself a Law, 10/17/1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Flyers for the Animal-of-the-Month-Club, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Of Pith and Vinegar-Book by Davis S. Brown, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Of Pith and Vinegar II- conclusion, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1938-1987; MS0001 Series 4; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 21, Box 22, Box 19, Box 20, Box 18, Box 17)
  This series contains correspondence to and from David S. Brown from 1938 through 1987, including both personal and professional correspondence.
  - Misc. Papers, 1982-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hassan El Tayeb, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - ASAE Committee, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rejections of Articles, 1983-1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Regarding Publishing, 1938-1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Regarding Publishing, 1971-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Regarding Publishing, 1981-1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Letters to and from children, 1956-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Letters, 1956-1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Letters DSB, 1959-1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Personal Letters DSB, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Articles (correspondence concerning), 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Personal, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Letters, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Robert Lovett Brown (3rd child), 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Family letters written by David S. Brown to his children and also his mother, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Letters written by Anne Brown to her mother-in-law and step-children, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Re: Estate of Myra S. Brown, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mother's estate, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Family letters (including some from the Lovetts to their daughter Evelyn Lovett Brown), 1972-1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Anne Brown's sister, Esther Moldawer, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Carbons, 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Letters, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - ASPA/Policy Issues, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Kettering Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - MLO Book permission to print, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - European trip, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Robert W. Brown, 1980-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - U.N. Correspondence: Mr. Banerjee and Kolchin, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Training materials used in classes, undated; MS0001 Series 5; 3 Linear feet (Box 28, Box 29, Box 27, Box 26, Box 25, Box 24, Box 23)
  This series contains lectures and readings used in David S. Brown's classes.
  - Misc. Lectures, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - DSB Lectures, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lectures, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - DSB-Lectures, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - DSB-Lectures, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - DSB Lectures, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - DSB Lectures, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - DSB Lectures, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Lectures, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Management materials, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Public Administration, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Lectures, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - DSB Lectures, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Management, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Basics of Management, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Organizations/Systems, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Human Factor, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Public Administration, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Development Administration, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Managing/Administering, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Supervising, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Key to Self-Help, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Testing Management I.Q., undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Problems in the Organization, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Work Motivation Factors, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Work Motivation Factors, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Rank Order, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Leadership We Prefer, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Why We Reject Leadership, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Macro/Micro, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Poor Decision, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Individual Development, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Some Statements Having To Do With Productivity, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - White Collar, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Manager's Responsibilities, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Basics of Management, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Barnard/Precepts, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - What To Do On the Job, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Supervisor Guidelines, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Human Factor, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Reorganization, the Health Department, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Management, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Specialists and Generalists: A Selection of Readings, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Program Ideas, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Good Management Papers, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - DSB Papers, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Papers-DSB, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Faculty articles from School of Government and Business Administration, MS0001 Series 6; 1 Linear feet (Box 29)
  This series contains articles written by other faculty at the School of Government and Business Administration.
  - The Thrifts Tomorrow (Handorf Reprint) 85-1R, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Robles 85-2R, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - D. Frame 85-3,4R, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Adams 85-5,6,7R, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Burdetsky and Katzman 85-8R, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Anconie 85-9R, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Englander 85-10R, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Eastaugh 85-11R, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Eastaugh 85-12R, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Katzman 85-13R, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Robles 85-14R, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Robles and Hozier 85-15R, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Southby 85-16R, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Fuller and Towles 85-17R, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Fuller and Towles 85-18R, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fuller 85-19R, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Lobuts and Pennewill 86-1R, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Lobuts and Pennewill 86-2R, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Lobuts and Pennewill 86-3R, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Newcomer 86-4R, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Alex Anconie 86-5R, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - William C. Adams 86-6R, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Michelle L. Slagle 86-7R, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Walter Hahn 86-8R, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Walter Hahn 86-9R, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Kathryn E. Newcomer 86-10R, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Kathryn E. Newcomer 86-11R, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Fuller, Stephen 86-12R, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - David Brown 86-13R, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Bingman, Charles F. 86-14R, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Jill F. Kasle 86-15R, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Fariborz Ghadar 86-16R, undated (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Raymond Rodosevich and Fernando Robles 86-17R, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Gary Crum 86-18R, undated (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Warren Greenberg 86-19R, undated (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Jill F. Kasle 86-20R, undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Dennis Gale 86-21R, undated (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Phillip Fanara, Jr. and Warren Greenberg 86-22R, undated (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - W. E. Halal 86-23R, undated (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Susan J. Tolchin 86-24R, undated (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - William C. Adams 86-25R, undated (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - William C. Adams 86-26R, undated (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Gary E. Popp and Herbert J. Davis 86-27R, undated (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - William E. Halal 86-28R, undated (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - William E. Halal 86-29R, undated (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Robles Sarathy 86-30R, undated (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - William Halal 86-31R, undated (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Newcomer, Caudle 86-32R, undated (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Fernando Robles 86-33R, undated (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Steven R. Eastaugh 86-34R, undated (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Peter B. Vaill 86-35R, undated (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Eastaugh 86-36R, undated (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Steven R. Eastaugh 86-37R, undated (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - William E. Halal 86-38R, undated (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Eastaugh 86-39, undated (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Lobuts and Pennewill 86-40R, undated (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Peter B. Vaill 86-41R, undated (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - SGBA Research Committee [1/2], 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - SGBA Research Committee [2/2], 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Auber Annual Surveys, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Research Information, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - David Brown, undated (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Management, undated (Box 29, Folder 63)
- Miscellaneous articles and manuscripts, MS0001 Series 7; 3.5 Linear feet (Box 35, Box 34, Box 33, Box 32, Box 31, Box 30, Box 36)
  This series contains a selection of David S. Brown's articles and manuscripts. Some are labeled duplicates. No attempt appears to have been made to arrange the articles. It also contains a dissertation from 1936 titled "The Public Advisory Board in the Federal Gov't."
  - Other Languages, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Papers from Pakistan, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Manuscripts, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Manuscripts, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Published Articles, 1970-1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Published Articles, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Published Articles DSB, 1960-1969 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Asian Forum, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Published Articles, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Published Articles, 1980-1989 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Chapters from Seeing It Through, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Published Articles, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Management, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Training and Management, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Building A Concert For Action, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Scope and Contents Note on David Brown Collection, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Management for the Many, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Some Quotations On Decision Making, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The Human Factor, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)